<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Medieval Patches (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.MedievalPatches</packageId>
  <author>Bennington</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/MedievalPatches</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter>
    <li>spoonshortage.ADogSaidAnimalProsthetics</li>
    <li>Fluffy.ColonyManager</li>
    <li>Porohkun.ConcreteWalls</li>
    <li>Ykara.EPOE</li>
    <li>vat.epoeforked</li>
    <li>zymex.medicaddons</li>
    <li>vindar.medievaltimes</li>
    <li>Haplo.Miscellaneous.Core</li>
    <li>Mlie.SimplyMoreBridges</li>
    <li>dninemfive.simpleconcrete</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Benningtons mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2177958478

- Should now only try to load patches if the corresponding mod is loaded

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/MedievalPatches][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/h5VwTNL.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
_______________________________________________________________

[b]This mod includes patches for a few mods that make them more “low tech” friendly. These include:[/b]

1. EPOE (Moved simple prosthetic research to medieval era, replaced electricity requirement from the simple prosthetic workbench with a wood fuel requirement.)
2. Concrete Walls *REQUIRES THE MEDIEVAL TIMES MOD AS WELL* (Moved concrete research to medieval era, made concrete slabs craftable at the blacksmith’s smelter from the Medieval Times mod instead of the vanilla electric smelter.)
3. A Dog Said... (Moved simple animal prosthetics research to medieval era, replaced electricity requirement from the animal prosthetic workbench with a wood fuel requirement.)
4. Colony Manager (Reflavored managing software research to be more low tech, added a simple research bench requirement, and moved it to the medieval era.)
5. Misc. Core (Disabled both the Railgun and the BrainPal.)
6. Medic Addons (Disabled industrial and spacer medical station add-ons)
7. Drug Lab (Research: Drug Production, has now been moved down to medieval tech (I suggest installing Medieval Medicines to Take Advantage of This))
8. Early Times Mod (This mod patches their integrated Medieval Times)
9. Simply Bridges (They had bridges in Medieval Times right?)
10. [WD] Simple Concrete *REQUIRES THE MEDIEVAL TIMES MOD AS WELL* (Incase you prefer this concrete solution over the other mod)

[b]Change Log:[/b]

7/31/20: Updated to 1.2, 1.1 is still compatible

7/26/20: Included Neceros Simply Bridges Medieval Patch

7/26/20 Update 2: Made a Patch for [WD] Simple Concrete Incase You Prefer His Iteration of Concrete Over The Other

[b]Other recommended mods for low tech game types:[/b]

1. Medieval Times (My personal favorite mod, and the reason I made Medieval World in the first place. The mod is spectacular, and it's creator, Vindar, is a absolute class act. This one is a literal game changer, and I can't recommend it enough.)
2. Fishing Industry (Adds fishing. Excellent mod in almost all games, but nearly essential for those tribal tundra games where food is extremely scarce.)
3. Simple Sidearms (Allows pawns to carry bow + melee weapon together.)
4. Defensive Positions (Adds the ability to draft pawns to a saved position. This one is a lifesaver for all the micromanagement it takes care of.)
5. No Power Comms Console (Replaces the comms console with a message raven, Game of Thrones style.)
6. Dubs Skylights (Very useful for making greenhouses.)
7. Firepit + Torch Sconce (Adds a fire pit and torch sconce that can be refueled instead of simply disappearing like the regular fire and torch)
8. Bridges (Not only useful for the bridges, but also allows you to place water tiles for that castle moat you’ve always dreamed of.)
9. Tilled Soil (Adds buildable soil for growing crops almost anywhere. Pairs very nicely with Dubs Skylights.)
10. Quarry (Adds an excellent end-game electricity free resource mining solution)
11. Misc. Bees'n'Honey (Adds beehives, honey, and brewable mead. Skyrim approved.)
12. Medieval Medicines (Adds Medieval Tech Medicines)
13. Medieval Lighting and Heating (Adds Medieval Themed Lighting and Heating)
14. Medieval Prosthetics (Adds more medieval themed prosthetics)
15. Medieval Cryptosleep (Adds Medieval Themed Cryptosleep Chamber)
16. Rimworld - Medieval Edition (Adds Medieval Themed Weapons/Armor/Factions/Items/Buildings
17. Arrows Please (Adds Medieval Themed Defense Solutions and Bows)
18. Not Only Just a Cannon (Adds Medieval Themed Defense Solutions)

[b]Suggested Load Order:[/b]

1. Core
2. Medieval Times
3. (any other mod that you intend to patch from the list)
5. Medieval Patches

If you have any feedback or suggestions for more medieval patches, please feel free to leave me a comment on the Steam Workshop

[b]Credit:[/b]

Tamais: Author of No Guns/Low Tech (Base for the patches)
Neceros: Medieval Patch for Simply Bridges
[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]</description>
</ModMetaData>